warframe.com 2019-12-12

# Warframe: Privacy Policy

## WARFRAME®   
PRIVACY POLICY

Last Edited: June 12, 2018

Digital Extremes Ltd.’s Privacy Policy 

Digital Extremes Ltd., located at 250 York Street, London, Ontario in London Ontario, N6A 6K2, (“we” or “us”) provides this website and is the controller of your personal data. Our representative in the European Union is RIVACY GmbH i.G. located at Hammerbrookstraße 90, 20097 Hamburg, Germany. 

Our data protection officer may be contacted at [ privacy@digitalextremes.com ](mailto:privacy@digitalextremes.com) . 

We strive to be transparent about how we collect and use your information. The following policy outlines how we collect, use, share, and protect your information. 

This policy applies to all of Digital Extremes Ltd’s games and services, including Warframe, as well as the following websites: [ https://www.digitalextremes.com ](https://www.digitalextremes.com/) , [https://www.warframe.com](https://www.warframe.com/)

###  Information we Collect 

As you engage with our products and services, sometimes you will be asked to provide us with personal information. The information that you are asked to provide and the reasons why you are asked to provide it will be made clear to you at the point we request it. Providing us with this information is entirely voluntary but if you choose not to provide it you may not be able to access some of our games or services. Here are examples of when we directly ask you to provide us with information: 

  * Account related data provided by you upon account creation, such as an email, account name and platform. 
  * Any information provided by you in connection with contacting our Customer Support services 
  * Information that is posted or commented on our forums and websites 
  * Information provided as a result of entering contests, competitions or answering survey questions. 

We also collect a variety of information from you automatically as a result of you using our services and through your interactions on our websites. Some of this information is collected anonymously while at other times it is collected and associated with other information you’ve already provided. In cases where this information is linked to your account information, or if the info collected can be used to trace back to a specific person, then we consider this information to be personal data. Here are examples of information what is collected automatically when you use our services: 

  * IP address 
  * Geographic location information 
  * Device information related to how you engage with our services 
  * In-game behaviors and progression stats 
  * Event data related to how your account information is modified or updated over time. 
  * Transactional data around virtual currency purchases and in-game purchases 
  * Advertising referral information when you sign up using one of our partner's ad campaigns. 
  * Cookie data regarding how you engage with our websites (see “Which Cookies we or third parties use” section below) 

###  How we use your information 

Our primary reason for collecting information from you is to provide you with our services and to improve and personalize those services. We may also use the information we collect for the following purposes: 

· To ensure that our websites are displayed to you in the most useful way possible 

· To help you if you need to contact our support services 

· To communicate with you regarding your account and your transactions with us and our partners 

· To better understand your engagement with our services and websites 

· To help keep our services secure and protect against fraud or other illicit activity 

· To send you emails regarding new updates, sales, and announcements 

· To customize marketing advertisements and promotional offers 

Our legal basis for collecting and processing the personal information described above will depend on the information being collected and the context for which we collect it, but will always fall into one of four categories; 1) for the purpose of performing a contract with you, 2) where the processing is in our legitimate interest and not overridden by your rights, 3) where we have your consent to do so, and 4) where we have a legal obligation. 

###  Which Cookies we or third parties use 

Some of the data processing operations about which we inform you in this Privacy Policy require that we or third parties use cookies. Below you will find a detailed list of these cookies: 

**Strictly necessary cookies and functionality cookies:** ****

**Cookie** ****

| 

**Description** ****

| 

**Purpose** ****

| 

**Duration** ****  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
_Landing_

| 

_To determine if it is your first time visiting our websites_

| 

_To redirect the user to the signup landing page_

| 

_1 year_  
  
_Logsig_

| 

_An encrypted value for forum single sign on_

| 

_Required for single sign on to forums_

| 

_1 day_  
  
_Gid_

| 

_Stores your user ID_

| 

_Required for single sign on to forums_

| 

_1 day_  
  
_Email_

| 

_Stores your email._

| 

_Required for single sign on to forums_

| 

_1 day_  
  
Third party cookies 

**3rd Party**

| 

**Cookie**

| 

**Description**

| 

**Purpose**

| 

**Duration**  
  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
_Google_

| 

__ga_

| 

_Google Analytics cookie which tracks visitor behaviour and measures site performance._

| 

_To analyse the use of and visits on our website._

| 

_2 years_  
  
_Google_

| 

__gaexp_

| 

_Google Analytics cookie which tracks visitor behaviour and measures site performance._

| 

_Used to determine a user's inclusion in an experiment and the expiry of experiments a user has been included in._

| 

_90 days_  
  
_Google_

| 

__gid_

| 

_Google Analytics cookie which tracks visitor behaviour and measures site performance._

| 

_To store and update a unique value for each page visited_

| 

_1 day_  
  
_Google_

| 

__gat_

| 

_Google Analytics cookie which tracks visitor behaviour and measures site performance._

| 

_Used to throttle the request rate - limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites_

| 

_1 day_  
  
_DoubleClick_

| 

__ar_v4_

| 

_DoubleClick advertising service from Google_

| 

_Tracking conversion rates for ads_

| 

_6 years_  
  
_Quantcast_

| 

__qca_

| 

_Quantcast digital advertising cookie_

| 

_For targeted advertising_

| 

_1 year_  
  
###  How we share your information 

We may need to share your information in the following circumstances: 

###  With your Consent 

We will share your information with our partners when we have obtained your consent to do so. We will inform you about our respective partners, the purpose of the data transfer and its legal basis in detail prior to obtaining your consent. 

###  Platform partners and payment providers 

As part of providing a global service, we frequently need to communicate your account information with our platform partners and our payment providers (such as Valve, Sony, Microsoft, Digital River, Xsolla, Rixty, Changyou and yCoins). These partners help us distribute our services and process transactions. 

###  Service partners 

We may share your information with our service partners (such as Akamai and Klavio) in connection with providing our services to you. The following activities may involve us sharing your personal information with a trusted partner: hosting, caching services, email delivery, player surveys, and other IT services. 

###  Support partners 

We may share your information with our customer support management partner (Zendesk) if you contact our support page and request assistance. 

###  Analytics partners 

We may share your information with our analytics partners (such as Google Analytics) in order to help us perform analysis on user behavior and better understand our players. The information being shared is typically anonymous. 

###  Marketing Partners 

We may share your information with some of our marketing partners (such as Facebook) in order for us to better serve ads to existing and future players. 

###  Our subsidiaries and affiliates 

We may share your information with our subsidiary (Digital Extremes US Inc.) or our parent company (Leyou Technologies Holdings Limited) in order to satisfy a legal or regulatory obligation, or to assist in our processing responsibilities. ****

###  Legal or Other Purposes 

We may share your information with law enforcement, government agencies and regulators in circumstances which may be required by law, or to defend our legal rights, or to protect your vital interests or those of another person. 

Third-party links   
Our websites contain links to third-party websites. Once you have been redirected to other websites, any information you provide is subject to said-third party websites’ Privacy Policy. 

###  How we protect your information 

Your information is protected by technical and organizational security measures appropriate to the nature of the information being collected. Only trained Digital Extremes employees have access to personal information and abide by our procedures and protocols. 

###  Data Retention 

In general, data is retained only as long as your account is active or as required through obligations relating to the operation of our business (bookkeeping, fraud prevention, and legal requirements). 

###  Your rights 

###  Right of Access 

You have the right to view a copy of the personal data we store on you free of charge. 

###  Right to Rectification 

At any time you can update your Account Information by logging in to your account profile on our website. If for whatever reason you believe the personal information we have about you is inaccurate or incomplete and requires changes, please notify us through our [Support](https://digitalextremes.zendesk.com/) page or by using the “How to contact us” section below. 

###  Right to Erasure 

You have the right to request that we delete Personal Data that we store on you. You can do this by contacting our [Support](https://digitalextremes.zendesk.com/) page on our website and requesting your account to be deleted. We ensure that all deletion requests are satisfied within one month upon receipt of your request. Please note that once an account is deleted there is no way to recover it. Some information may be retained by us to the extent we need to satisfy a legal requirement or for security purposes. Some information will also be retained anonymously. 

###  Right to withdraw Consent 

Some of our processing is based on your consent. You can withdraw your consent at any time without impact to data processing activities that have taken place before such withdrawal or to any other existing legal justification of the processing activity in question. 

###  **Right to Object**

**You have the right to object to us processing your Personal Data at any time when the processing is based on our legitimate interests (and not, for example, a legal obligation) on grounds relating to your particular situation. If you object we will no longer process your Personal Data unless there are compelling and prevailing legitimate grounds for the processing or the data is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims. If you do not want us to process your Personal Data for marketing activities, you can make those changes on your data permissions page** [here](https://warframe.com/user/data-permissions) **or contact us any time via e-mail at** [ privacy@digitalextremes.com ](mailto:privacy@digitalextremes.com) **.**

###  Right to Proceed and to take Legal Actions 

If you are not satisfied with our processing of your personal information, you also have the right to make a complaint to the relevant supervisory authority. Please see [ here ](http://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/item-detail.cfm?item_id=612080) for the relevant contact details. 

You also have the right to take legal actions in relation to any breach of your rights regarding the processing of your Personal Data. 

###  Further Rights 

Where processing of your Personal Data is either based on your consent or necessary for the performance of a contract with you and processing is carried out by automated means, you have the right to receive the Personal Data you have provided in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format or to have your personal data transmitted directly to another company, where technically feasible (data portability). 

Further, you have the right not to be subject to any automatic individual decisions which produce legal effects on you or similarly significantly affects you. 

###  How to Exercise Your Rights 

You can exercise your rights by contacting our [Support](https://digitalextremes.zendesk.com/) page or by using the “How to contact us” section below. We satisfy these requests within one month upon receipt of your request. If the request affects the rights and privacy of others we reserve the right to refuse to act on the request. If your request is manifestly unfounded or excessive, we reserve the right to charge a reasonable fee or to refuse to act on the request. 

Please note that we may need to request information from you to confirm your identity and establish your entitlement to these rights. 

###  Children 

None of our services or content on our websites are designed or intended for children under 16 years of age. Our content is in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and will never be directed at children under 16 years of age. If you are under 16 years of age, you are not permitted to access the websites or games unless your parent or guardian has provided express consent and accepts this Agreement along with all applicable end-user or similar license agreements on your behalf prior to your use of the websites or games. Please see our[Terms of Service](http://warframe.com/terms) and [End-User License Agreement](https://www.warframe.com/eula) for additional information. 

###  Updates to this policy 

From time to time we may update this policy for various reasons, including regulatory changes, changes in the scope of our services and advancements in our processes. We will take appropriate measures to inform you in the event of a significant change to this policy. Please refer to the date at the top of the page to see when the policy was last updated. 

###  How to contact us 

If you have any questions or would like to make a request in connection with your rights listed above, please contact our [Support](https://digitalextremes.zendesk.com/) team through our websites or send us an email at [ Privacy@digitalextremes.com ](mailto:Privacy@digitalextremes.com) .
